(Raj:)Like, I love me
some Clooney.
(Leonard:)Don't say that to anyone.
(Penny:)Thank you so much
for helping us, Stuart.
Oh, I-I was just
(Stuart:)glad to be invited.
(Stuart:)To be honest, I don't always
feel like I'm part of the group.
(Penny:)Okay, sweetie,
we're on the clock here.
(Penny:)Can you hate yourself
and frost at the same time?
(door opens)
Hello, I hope I'm not too early.
(Bernadette:)No, no, no. Come on in.
And how is the radiant
mommy-to-be?
(Bernadette:)Doing great.
Y-You're pregnant?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Stuart:)Sounds like something
(Stuart:)a member of the group
might know.
(Penny:)Yeah, birthday party first.
(Penny:)Pity party later.
(Leonard:)Are you crazy?
(Leonard:)How can you put Michael Keaton
(Leonard:)in front of Christian Bale?
(Adam West:)Oh, please.
(Adam West:)Even my poodles know
Bale's overrated.
Thank you!
(Raj:)That's why I say
Keaton's number one.
(Raj:)He brought a sense
of humor to the role.